Resynchronized By aReN (RaviKant)
'This is Durban's
biggest race track.'
'Here, dreams ride on horsebacks.'
'And to turn these
dreams into reality..
..people live, die, and kill too.'
'Today is the
season's biggest race.'
Durban Cup.
'This is Ranvir Singh!'
'Here, Ranvir
Singh's horses run too.'
'Ranvir likes races a lot.'
'Not to win, but to live it.'
'Race is his life.'
'Stallions.'
'This ranch house is owned by..
..Ranvir Singh and his
younger brother, Rajiv Singh.'
'Horses of the finest
breed are bred here.'
'They are trained.'
'Bred.'
'They are sold.'
'And they run in the races too.'
'Other than races,
Ranvir Singh's passion..
..is outdoor sports.'
'Especially, something
that involves, excitement..
..thrill, danger..
and threat to life!'
'He lives life on the edge.'
'This is Ranvir's jockey, Monto!'
'Monto controls all
of Ranvir's horses.'
'This is Ranvir's rival,
Kabir Ahuja!'
'He is a very big bookie, too.'
'His horses take
part in the races, too.'
'lf there is anyone
who can contest Ranvir..
..then it's only Kabir.'
'Horses run alone in the races.'
'But in real life, a
person needs a companion.'
'This is Sonia, an upcoming model.'
'She is in search of a person
who can immerse her in his heart.'
'Often, love starts
through the eyes.'
'And it increases
with regular meetings.'
'Both have come quite
close to each other.'
'They only need to propose. '
'This is Rajiv Singh!'
'Ranvir's younger brother.'
'People usually have
tea when they get up.'
Get up sir, it's morning. Beer.
'But to get rid of the hangover
of the night, Rajiv drinks beer.'
Rajiv isn't interested
in his family business.
'Ranvir loves his brother a lot.'
'But Rajiv loves alcohol.'
On which horse?
- White Lightning.
'Sophia, Ranvir's secretary!'
'Sophia loves Ranvir.'
Thank you, l'd forgotten!
'But Ranvir thinks
it's just her efficiency.'
Hi Rajeev.
- Hi.
lt is at the top most.
- Oh yes!
'Ranvir's horse, White Lightning..
..is the hot
favourite of today's race.'
'Ranvir has betted a lot
of money on today's race.'
'Today, on it's win, a lot of
Ranvir's problems will be solved.'
Come on!
Come on! Buck up!
This is cheating!
l will not spare him!
Thank you very much.
l hope you won some money.
Sign here, sir.
l will see you in the office.
- Thank you, sir.
Bad luck, Ranvir.
You lost.
l am sorry.
Don't be. l celebrate my defeat too.
Really? lf you throw a
party then do invite me.
He laughs a lot.
When a person laughs a lot,
he also cries a lot.
Yes, thanks for coming.
That's the money.
- Thank you.
He's leaving.
Who can stop someone's departure?
♫ Wake up and feel the pace. ♫
♫ Don't stop, there
is a lot in the race. ♫
♫ Race. ♫
♫ Wake up and feel the pace. ♫
♫ Don't stop, there
is a lot in the race. ♫
♫ Race. ♫
'The lives of these 4 people..
..would have
continued the same way.'
'lf this incident
wouldn't have taken place..
..today, on the 7th of October.'
Great!
Fantastic!
Everything is normal!
Even after such a big accident,
you are normal.
lt is a miracle.
No, no doctor it is not a miracle.
My brother is a very tough guy.
- lsn't that right?
Yes!
So, how much money are
you going to charge Ronny?
What?
l mean, for how many days
will you keep Ronny here?
At least 15-20 days.
That will pass by soon.
Fine, Mr. Rajiv
whenever you are free..
..come and meet me in my office.
l need you to sign some papers.
- Sure, doctor.
We will meet in the evening!
- Sure.
Nurse, come with me.
Sit.
Ronny, are you fine? Get well soon!
l don't know how to say all that.
Just remember one thing.
Without you, l will
be left all alone.
Don't worry, Rajiv.
Nothing will happen to me.
ls it paining?
Yes!
Not that, have a few sips of this..
..everything will vanish!
Very funny!
Rajiv!
- Sorry.
l'll go and complete
the formalities, okay?
You got to be fine.
Hello!
Cheers!
To my brother's long life!
Cheers.
- Give it to everyone.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
l am sorry l am late.
Those whom we wait for,
often come late.
And often, those who
come late are wonderful.
This is my younger brother Rajiv.
Hi!
- Nice to meet you. - Me, too.
This is my P.A Sophia!
Hi, nice to meet you.
And this is my friend, Sonia!
Mr. Mickey has come.
Please excuse me.
Rajiv will look after you.
Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
Can l get you a drink?
Sure.
This way.
Now l know why Ronny doesn't drink.
After seeing you, he doesn't
need any other intoxication.
You are praising me a lot.
lf you see from my point
of view, you'll know..
..l'm praising you very little.
By the way, what do you
think about love at first sight?
lt saves time!
lt saves time! l love that.
You know we think alike.
Ronny never mentioned about you.
How long have you known each other?
About 2-3 months.
Anything serious?
Don't say yes!
Don't say yes! Please.
Why are you asking?
Because.. you know what?
Give me one minute.
Make him agree.
Hello, where is Rajiv!
- l don't know.
He said he'll be back in a minute.
Shall l tell you one thing?
You two are quite different.
When it's about girls,
he's faster than you!
Not bad.
He has impressed you a
lot in the first meeting.
♫ Akbar! ♫
♫ The entire world is enthralled. ♫
♫ lt is such a wonderful encounter. ♫
♫ There is restlessness. ♫
♫ l am finally saying
what was in my heart. ♫
♫ Come in my arms, charm me.. ♫
♫ ..come baby shake it,
shake it some more. ♫
♫ O baby, rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ Rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ That's the show before you! ♫
♫ That's the show behind you! ♫
♫ Rock! Rock! Rock! Rock! ♫
♫ Lost in my dreams. ♫
♫ Time has stopped. ♫
♫ They make a gesture to me slyly. ♫
♫ l won't say anything. ♫
♫ l will keep tight-lipped. ♫
♫ l will unite the hearts slyly! ♫
♫ Lock eyes, excite me, come
shake it, shake it some more! ♫
♫ O baby, rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ Rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ That's the show before you! ♫
♫ That's the show behind you! ♫
♫ Rock! Rock! Rock! Rock! ♫
♫ My beloved, what
has to happen here.. ♫
♫ ..let it happen! Let it happen! ♫
♫ Let me live this moment. ♫
♫ Let me savor your eyes. ♫
♫ Let me immerse in
these wonderful thoughts. ♫
♫ Rock the jamboree.
Forget everything. ♫
♫ Come shake it, shake it some more! ♫
♫ O baby, rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ Rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ That's the show before you! ♫
♫ That's the show behind you! ♫
♫ Rock! Rock! Rock! Rock! ♫
♫ Shake it! Shake it! Shake it!
Shake it! Shake it! Shake it! ♫
♫ The entire world is enthralled. ♫
♫ lt is such a wonderful encounter. ♫
♫ There is restlessness. ♫
♫ l am finally saying
what was in my heart. ♫
♫ Come in my arms, charm me.. ♫
♫ ..come baby shake it,
shake it some more. ♫
♫ O baby, rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ Rock the dance floor! ♫
♫ That's the show before you! ♫
♫ That's the show behind you! ♫
♫ Rock! Rock! Rock! Rock! ♫
Brother!
Are you done? Or should
l bring another bottle?
Did you have fun?
Brother, people say that
alcohol is slow poison.
ls it true?
Yes, it's true.
Very good. l don't
want to die early.
Come inside.
Come on.
People also say, if
you drink too much..
..you don't remain in your senses.
ls it correct?
- Yes, correct.
Very good. We don't have to go to
the moon that we need our senses!
Careful!
Sorry brother.
People also say that love is
more intoxicating than alcohol.
lt's all true, Rajiv.
Everything will be right,
come on now lets go inside.
No, no.
Once Sonia enters my life.
l will.. stop drinking..
..forever!
She is beautiful.
She is really..
Just.. just.. just
remember what l am saying.
Forever!
Good morning!
Anything urgent?
Yes, you have to submit some
documents in the excise department.
Your signatures are needed.
Take a look.
You are looking good.
l am talking about the documents.
You check them.
Anything else?
- Yes, the bank manager had called.
You have to pay 4
installments of the ranch mortgage.
Okay, do one thing.
Contact any estate
agency in Cape Town.
Yes.
- l have a property there.
l want to sell it and
clear all my bank dues.
Okay.
- As soon as possible.
Good morning ma'am!
Good morning.
Sam, take this back.
And bring a glass of
water with two disprins.
But Rajiv sir has this
drink every morning.
Sam..
- Right, sir.
Carry on, l will meet you
later in the office. - Okay!
Hello. Are you alright.
l had a bit too much yesterday,
my head is paining.
ls that it, or is
there something else?
Where is the beer?
You can get rid of your
hangover with this too.
Remember what you said yesterday?
What?
That, if Sonia enters your life,
you will stop drinking.
l was drunk, brother.
People usually tell the
truth when they are drunk.
How can she ever enter the
life of a drunkard like me?
What if she does?
How can she brother?
Then l will stop drinking.
Fine. lf you want to
have lunch with Sonia..
..then come to club,
exactly at 1 :00.
Don't be late.
Lunch, with Sonia.
- Yes, sir.
Sir, newspaper.
And Sam, call me exactly
at 1 o'clock on my mobile.
Fine, sir.
Well, this is a pleasant surprise!
Hi guys.
What are you doing here?
Had a meeting with a client.
As we were going back,
we spotted you.
Mind if l join you?
- Come, sit.
You are looking great.
And you are
looking very fresh today.
Rajiv, there must have
been a shortage of drinks..
..in the party
yesterday because of you.
Do you always..
- Oh God!
Look.
There are always two
reasons for drinking alcohol.
Happiness or sorrows.
Yesterday, l had both the reasons.
Happiness, because l
met you yesterday.
And l was sad, because
we didn't we meet earlier.
Come on, stop now.
By the way, Sonia, what
is your plan for today?
Nothing great.
Then let's make it great.
Let's have lunch together.
Sure.
Excuse me.
Hi Priya!
Sweetheart, l am
so sorry, l am late.
Sweetheart!
Come on baby, don't get angry.
Okay, let's do one thing.
We will have lunch
and dinner together.
Happy?
l love you, bye.
Who is Priya?
- My girlfriend.
She has returned from
New York after 3 months.
And because of my work..
..l forgot l was
supposed to have lunch with her.
She is very angry. l will
have to go and appease her.
After all, it is the
question of my entire life.
l will go too.
Why? Do you have any
problem in having lunch with me?
lt's nothing like that.
Then?
Okay!
Great!
Good.
Then l will leave.
Have fun!
You guys have fun.
- We will.
Wow, how nice!
Eating alone is so great!
Now you will say
that you're with me.
The truth is, just
like you are with me..
..so are all the other
customers in this restaurant.
No one talks to me, no
one laughs at my jokes.
What has happened to you today?
Why are you so quiet?
lt is nothing like that.
Won't you tell your friend?
Love starts with friendship!
But not every
friendship turns into love.
Anyways, l am leaving.
l have my fashion show tomorrow.
l have to go for the rehearsals.
Won't you invite your friend?
l have sent the
invitation to your house.
Now you will come.
Do come.
No problem. Come, l will drop you.
l have brought my car.
Fantastic! Then you give me a lift.
♫ You have enchanted
me at first sight. ♫
♫ l have lost my heart to you. ♫
♫ God knows what will happen next. ♫
♫ Let's live this moment together. ♫
♫ l am here, you are here. ♫
♫ Come in my arms. ♫
♫ O darling, come forget
both the worlds in my arms. ♫
♫ Baby, l love you! ♫
♫ Baby, l love you, so! ♫
♫ Oh l love you! ♫
♫ l love you! ♫
♫ l love you, so! ♫
♫ Baby, l love you! ♫
♫ All l wish for is your love. ♫
♫ Even a moment without
you is unimaginable. ♫
♫ My heartbeats desire only you! ♫
♫ You are my relief! ♫
♫ You are my love! ♫
♫ When l found you, l lost myself. ♫
♫ O darling, come forget
both the worlds in my arms. ♫
♫ Ladies and gentlemen, the
designer of the evening. ♫
♫ Mr. Almanor! ♫
♫ Baby, l love you! ♫
♫ Baby, l love you, so! ♫
♫ Oh l love you! ♫
♫ l love you! ♫
♫ l love you, so! ♫
Which drink will you have?
You know l don't drink.
Rajiv, so soon we have
come so close to each other.
Let's get married.
How can we get married?
Why?
Why? Because for getting married,
there should be love.
You think l don't love you.
No.
Come on, now stop joking.
l am not joking. l am serious.
How can l fall in love
with a girl like you?
And after reading this,
not just me..
..but no one will be
ready to marry you.
What is this?
Your bio-data!
The story from your
childhood till today.
You've been fooling people till now.
Sonia, beautiful name.
An orphanage of Mumbai
gave you this name..
..not your parents.
And till the age of 15,
you did such great deeds..
..that the court sent
you to the remand home.
At the age of 16, you
tried to flee from there.
And when you were caught,
you falsely accused..
..an old rector, that he
was trying to molest you.
What is this?
He is still in prison.
Then you became a bar dancer.
The owner of the bar
was crazy about you.
Anyone can be.
But you took undue advantage of it.
One day, you were about to
flee with the bar money..
..when the owner caught you.
And you killed him.
You hit him with a
bottle on his head. Oh God!
You are dangerous.
But the testimony of an
N.R.l lover saved you.
You came to South
Africa with him, right.
Rajiv, l wanted to tell
you everything myself.
But l was afraid,
that l might lose you.
Lose me! Nice!
What do you think? That l just
received this file from the courier?
l have been keeping a watch on you..
..since you have been eyeing Ranvir.
Come to the point.
What do you want?
That which you want.
Money!
The property for which
you have entrapped Ranvir..
..is mortgaged to the bank.
But l have a plan worth 100 million.
lf you help me, l will
give you 20 million.
How do you have so much money?
My father, whom l
hated all my life..
..did one good thing before dying.
He took out insurance
policy worth 50 million each..
..in the name of both the brothers.
lf Ranvir dies in an accident..
..then under the
double indemnity clause..
..l will get 100 million.
Wow!
My file is nothing compared to you.
l never saw a lowly man like you..
..who can kill his
own brother for money!
There is no need to be amazed.
Ranvir says himself,
that he loves me so much..
..that he can even die for me.
l am just fulfilling his desire.
lf your plan is ready..
..then what was the
need to put up a charade..
..of falling in love with me?
Because our love should
look natural to Ranvir.
What do l have to do now?
Marry me.
Don't worry. This marriage
will be a business deal.
And then?
First thing first, baby.
Are you in, or are you out!
l am in.
Thank you.
What's the right time?
Sir, exactly 2 minutes 7 seconds.
That's 7 seconds more.
Sam, yesterday l asked you
not to sign some papers.
Yes sir.
- Bring those papers.
Right, sir.
Hi Ranvir!
l think you are fond of
horses more than anyone else.
That's not it, Kabir, l
am quite fond of you too.
That's a good one,
that's a good joke.
Come to the point, why
did you want to meet me?
l have heard that this stud
farm is mortgaged to the bank.
lf you want, l can get it released.
Other than the
settlement with the bank..
..l am ready to give
you 10 million dollars.
Sell this stud farm to me.
l have often heard, those
who have a small brain..
..often talk big.
l didn't understand.
That's a good quality of yours.
You are ignorant.
These horses, this stud
farm run through my blood.
lt's not for sale. l
will never sell them.
Sir, papers.
Can l borrow your pen please?
Excuse me, that's my pen.
Thank you.
My offer is still open.
Think about it once more.
Kabir, l think
before taking a decision.
l don't think after
taking a decision.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Sir, in the next race, our horse
Blue Bolt is the hot favourite.
People have betted the most on him.
And on the rest of the horses?
2-3 million have been betted
on the rest of the horses.
And on number 12?
What?
l am talking about Ranvir's horse.
- Ranvir's horse is new.
The rate is 10 to 1 !
10 to 1 !
Bet all my money on Ranvir's horse.
But sir.. 20 million!
The next race is set.
My observation is
that after my horse..
..Ranvir's horse is the second best.
And my horse will slow down
just before the finish line.
Ranvir will lose
in spite of winning.
You mean, Ranvir's horse
will win and we will earn money?
You are right.
Good idea, sir.
Thank you.
Sophia.
Bet 4 million on Kabir's horse.
Won't we bet on your own horse?
Please just do as l say.
Horse no.12 Rising Star,
owned by Ranvir Singh.
We've got no.6 owned by Kabir..
..Blue Bolt are the
main contenders inside..
ls everything fine?
- Yes.
Very, very fast indeed.
They are all set.
lt is horse no.6, Blue
Bolt towards the lead.
lt's about to lead
the quarter in the 9..
Come on, Blue Bolt!
Come on!
O my God.
We are ruined sir!
We had taken a
betting of 50 million.
We will have to pay 80 million.
And the 20 million that
we bet on Ranvir's horse..
..we have lost that too.
Please, please, leave me alone..
..please, please leave me alone!
This is my pen.
Microphone!
And this is yours.
You slowed down your horse.
l slowed down my horse a bit more.
lt's your bad luck that you won.
By the way, l have
arranged a party today..
..to celebrate my defeat!
Do come.
lf you wanted, you could
have betted on your horse..
..and won more.
Victory and defeat is not
just about money, Sophia.
lf someone defeats and
kills me, l can tolerate that.
But l can never forgive
someone who deceives me.
Rajiv!
What happened?
l proposed to Sonia today.
And?
And.. she said yes!
Yes, she said yes.
That's great! That's great!
l want that too.
♫ Baby, l love you. ♫
♫ Forever. ♫
♫ My nights are not lonely anymore.. ♫
♫ And my stars are
like shining anymore. ♫
Rajiv,
congratulations on your wedding.
Careful.
Ronny, you are still awake!
You promised you
will never drink again.
Brother, l didn't want to drink.
My friends forced me.
l am telling the truth, believe me.
You have deceived me.
Now l cannot trust you.
Don't say that.
l will never drink again,
l swear on you.
Do you know the
meaning of this oath?
lf you ever touch
alcohol again, l will die.
That's why l have
taken such a big oath!
Go!
She is waiting for you.
How did you like my performance?
Your brother already
rewarded you for that.
l could hear the echo
of the clap till here.
Let's celebrate. Cheers.
No baby, drinking is
injurious to our plan.
lf we unknowingly make
even a small mistake..
..Ronny won't even give
us a chance to apologise.
ln this game, the
hunter can die too.
Then why put up a
charade of drinking?
This will happen everyday.
l want Ronny to realize that
he has made a big mistake..
..by getting you
married to a drunkard.
l see. What's the plan ahead?
l think we should call it a night.
Why? Don't you trust your wife?
What can l say?
Your bio-data is such.
That's why, l can't trust
anyone else other than myself.
By the way, our marriage was a deal.
But if you want,
anything can happen.
lt's not a bad idea.
But l don't mix
business with pleasure. Okay?
Whenever you are ready, baby.
Ranvir, the estate agent
had called from Cape Town.
A client is ready
to buy our property.
The deal can be finalised in 2 days.
l have booked 2
tickets for Cape Town.
Fine.
l need your
signature on some papers.
Anything else?
l've been observing
since a few days..
..that you are a bit disturbed.
What is it?
Rajiv has started drinking again.
After the marriage, there
hasn't been a single day..
..when he hasn't come home drunk.
l feel sad for Sonia.
l don't know how she
must be going through it.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Yes, l will just send the file.
l'll just be back.
Wow!
Lovely weather!
ln such weather, men
want only two things.
A cold beer and a hot babe.
l have already told you, l
don't mix business with pleasure.
l am not talking about myself.
Tonight you will
have to go to Ranvir.
And this time, it's purely business.
Good boy.
What are you doing here?
l want to talk to you
urgently about Rajiv.
Sonia, don't misunderstand Rajiv.
He loves you a lot.
Rajiv loves only
alcohol and no one else.
ln the last 15 days,
there has been..
..no relationship between us..
..which a husband and wife have.
You have ruined my life, Ranvir.
Why did you hide from me
that your brother is a drunkard?
lf l had known, that
he will break his oath..
..then, my love..
- You loved me.
How nice.
She is acting better than me.
Why.. why did you hide it?
Why?
l am sorry Sonia, l
made a terrible mistake.
l am paying for your mistake!
l need you.
What an era!
Marriage with the younger brother..
..and the wedding night,
with the elder brother.
Cheers!
Ranvir, my granny says..
..a girl is lucky, when people
think about her in her absence too.
And she's is unlucky, when
people think about something else..
..even her presence.
And l think l am unlucky.
Why do you say that?
Because l thought, being with me..
..you will forget all
your problems and tensions.
But you..
Tell me. How do you find me?
You are the closest to me.
l don't know what l
would do without you.
Really?
You've made my evening.
lt felt very nice to
hear what you said.
But it would have felt
better if you would have said it..
What?
♫ Touch! ♫
♫ O slowly, touch me!
Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ Touch me! Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ O slowly, touch me!
Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly, hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ Touch me! Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly, hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ l am waiting only for you. ♫
♫ l love only you. ♫
♫ You have put me on a high. ♫
♫ l don't have any
control on myself. ♫
♫ l am waiting only for you. ♫
♫ l love only you. ♫
♫ l am restless for you. ♫
♫ l don't have any
control on myself. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Touch me! Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly, hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ The pain doesn't lessen. ♫
♫ The distance troubles me. ♫
♫ l might lose control. ♫
♫ You are under my oath. ♫
♫ The pain doesn't lessen. ♫
♫ The distance troubles me. ♫
♫ l might lose control. ♫
♫ You are under my oath. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Touch me! Touch me! Touch me! ♫
♫ O slowly, kiss me!
Kiss me! Kiss me! ♫
♫ O slowly, hold me!
Hold me! Hold me! ♫
♫ O slowly.. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you my beloved,
in this world.. ♫
♫ ..l am all alone. ♫
♫ Without you.. ♫
Why have you come here?
l was missing you.
Listen to me, forget
everything that happened yesterday..
..it was a mistake.
Mistake! We love each other.
We used to!
Whatever happened, it's over.
Ronny, l want to live with
you and not your brother.
Please tell him
about our relationship.
l will divorce him and
we will get married.
Are you out of your mind?
That's not possible!
Fine! lf you can't tell him,
then l will tell him.
You won't do anything like that!
What next?
The gun is ready. All we
need to do is press the trigger.
Ronny, l am going to
kill that lowly man!
l swear to God, l am
going to kill him!
What's the matter Rajiv?
Whom are you talking about?
Sonia! She is having
an affair with someone.
l will kill that dirty woman!
That's ridiculous Rajiv!
Sonia is not like that.
lt's a fact!
She slyly goes to
meet someone everyday.
Last night, she
returned at 2 o'clock.
When l asked, she
said wherever l go..
..whomever l meet, what's it to you?
Rajiv, can l say something?
Before accusing Sonia, think
of what you have done with her.
lt has been so many
days since your marriage.
Have you given her a
single moment of happiness?
What are you talking about?
l am a woman, that's
why l can tell you..
..she is doing all this
to grab your attention.
And you are suspecting her.
lt's all nonsense.
l know she is having an affair.
And l will surely catch that man!
Sonia, good that you have come.
l am very confused.
Tell me, which one
is the best photo.
After Ranvir's death, we will
have to give it in the newspapers.
Dear brother, we
will never forget you.
All that will be later.
But how will we kill Ranvir?
What are you saying?
l will kill my elder brother.
l want the 100 million of
the insurance money, fool.
Brother will have to
die in an accident.
But how?
You want to know my plan?
Actually it's very simple.
The day brother
returns from Cape Town..
..l will go the terrace
of the office building..
..to commit suicide.
And exactly at 6:30,
l will call him..
..and tell him,
brother l have found out..
..that my wife is
having an affair with you.
And to clear your path,
l am committing suicide.
That poor guy loves me a lot.
He will instantly come
running to the terrace to save me.
And when he tries to save me..
..you will push him from the back.
He will lose his balance and..
And our bank balance.
lt's a brilliant plan.
First marriage with
the brother's girlfriend.
Then put a charade of
being drunk all the time.
Then your wife's
affair with your brother.
And then in the end, a
charade of committing suicide.
And then an accident.
lt's a brilliant plan.
Rajiv has taken care of
all the minor details.
But he has forgotten one thing.
l am his elder brother.
So what is your plan now?
Rajiv has worked
hard over this plan.
l don't want to hurt
him by changing the plan.
The plan will remain the same.
There will be a minor change.
l won't die, he will.
Yes, this is Ranvir speaking.
l want to meet you.
What is the status of the
flight arriving from Cape Town?
Thank you.
Ranvir's flight has landed.
The countdown begins.
The three days l spent
with you in Cape Town..
..l will never forget them.
They were the most
wonderful days of my life.
Same here.
Bye.
Very punctual.
Hello brother.
Ronny, you filthy man!
You are the one having
an affair with Sonia!
l've found out! lt's you, you fool!
Listen Rajiv, it's not
what you think it is.
l can explain everything.
Where are you?
On the office terrace you fool!
l am about to jump from here!
l am going to commit suicide!
Look Rajiv, you are surely mistaken.
Keep quiet! l am mistaken!
Sonia told me this herself!
Why are you telling this? Sonia is
your wife. She loves you very much.
Aren't you ashamed of
sleeping with your brother's wife?
l couldn't even think
you would deceive me.
Don't be mad.
Stay there, l am coming.
There is no need to come!
What explanation will you give?
That you made a mistake?
The only thing l regret, Ronny, is
that my own brother deceived me!
No Rajiv, that's not true.
You cheated me, backstabbed me.
Now, l have got nothing to live for.
Listen to me, Rajiv.
l know l have made a mistake.
Mistake!
Sleeping with your
younger brother's wife..
..is just a mistake for you?
What?
You said she is a
good friend of yours!
You should've told me if
you liked her so much..
..l wouldn't have married her.
First get down from here.
Then l will explain everything.
l still love you Ronny.
But 20 million dollars
is a very big amount.
l am sorry.
l guess this is where
we say goodbye, Ronny.
Mini! RD's assistant!
She is good at office work!
But she doesn't
understand RD's feelings.
RD!
lnspector Robert D'costa!
Now we will have fun!
Welcome, sir! Welcome! We
were waiting for you, sir!
Are you inviting me just like that..
..or is somebody getting married..
..and you've
called me here to dance?
No, sir. Actually it's the
lndian community's case..
..so we were 100 per cent sure that
the department will send you, sir.
First, tell me.
Yes, sir.
What about Alfonso mangoes?
Alfonso?
Yes. You were going to get
Alfonso mangoes for me from lndia!
What about that?
l forgot, sir!
You all don't pay
attention to your work!
How will you get promoted?
Spoilt my mood!
From which floor did
he do the high jump?
Sir, from 20th floor.
Great! People jump from a
height to reach to the moon.
He went further away!
Why did he commit suicide?
Sir, actually it's not a
suicide but an accident case.
Any eyewitness?
The victim's brother
and sister-in-law!
lt means when he was
falling from above..
..his brother and sister-in-law
were bidding him farewell!
Sir, l don't know.
But they both are
still upstairs, sir.
Then what are we doing downstairs?
Waiting for them to fall?
Let's go, Mini.
Let's interrogate them.
Maybe they've ordered
Alfonso mangoes from lndia.
Come on. Let's go.
Sir, he is Mr. Rajiv
Singh and his wife Sonia.
Okay. Go.
Hi! l am RD. Robert D'costa.
l am the investigating
officer of this case..
..and she is my assistant Mini.
l want to ask you a few questions.
Go ahead.
Can you tell me how
this accident took place?
This was not an accident.
l killed my brother.
Everything happened because of me.
Relax, Mr. Rajiv. Cool down.
Thank you. Will you have it?
No. You drink it.
l should be thanking you.
You accepted your crime so quickly.
Officer, this is not
what my husband meant.
Actually he is an alcoholic.
He thinks his drinking habit is
responsible for his brother's death.
lt was an accident.
Sir, if his wife had not been here,
he'd have been hanged.
Absolutely right! He
escaped because of his wife.
Often, people die
because of their wife.
Look, Mr. Rajiv.
lf you think that your
brother's death was an accident..
..then how is it
connected to your drinking?
Because of my bad habit of betting..
..Ranvir had incurred a
heavy loss in business.
He had to mortgage his ranch house.
And he had to sell Cape
Town's ancestral property too.
Because of that depression,
l started drinking a lot.
l thought that l am
responsible for all our problems.
So l decided to commit suicide.
At the last moment..
at the last moment..
..Ranvir came to save me.
Unfortunately he lost his balance.
And he fell down.
Sir, the man who
wanted to die, survived..
..and the man who had
come to save him, died!
That's strange!
Mini, l've told you many times..
..not to talk strangely
in front of strangers.
Do it when you are alone.
Just now he lost his brother.
You are hurting his feelings
more by talking like this.
Sorry, Mr. Rajiv.
My assistant is not
intelligent like your wife.
l can understand what
you are going through.
lt's quite late. Go and rest.
Come.
l hope it had happened
as you said, Mr. Rajiv.
Let's go, Mini.
Mini, hearing him what did
you feel? Where's the bag gone?
You know sir?
- Yes.
l remembered my uncle. He
died due to drinking too.
He used to drink a lot?
No, sir. A liquor
drum fell on his head!
l have observed that liquor
kills non-drinkers and not drinkers.
Mini, l was asking
you if you thought..
..he was lying or telling the truth?
The truth, sir.
You thought he was lying?
Mini, the first rule
of investigation is..
..not to trust your eyes and ears.
Just trust your mind.
Sir, it means you don't
think it was an accident?
Where there is big
money involved, baby..
..accidents are waiting to happen!
Correct! But why
didn't l understand that?
Because there is a problem with you.
What, sir?
l will tell you some other time.
Listen. By tomorrow morning..
..l want Sonia's,
Ranvir's and Rajiv's biography.
Now hold this banana
and get in the car.
l will eat it
peacefully inside. Come on!
Come! Come, Mr. Rajiv. Come!
Will you have sugarcane?
Actually this is to be sucked on.
But it doesn't feel right
to ask if you'll suck on it.
lnspector, what was the need to
call me for body identification?
l know that this accident
took place in front of you..
..but we have to
follow the procedure.
lsn't he your brother?
Yes.
You both are really strong.
Generally people either
faint or turn their face..
..after such a sight.
We have to be strong.
Now he has to look after the
office, house, everything.
That's right.
When can we claim the body?
Until the investigation is over..
..we can't give you the body.
Go to the office, l'll come there.
l want to interrogate your staff.
Come.
Sir, you are very strong.
You are having
sugarcane at such a time!
What has strength got to do with it?
The dead body won't
take my sugarcane!
My heart is still beating fast.
ls that so? Let me see.
Sir, what's the time?
Why?
Sir, we have to go
to Rajiv's office.
Mini, there won't be any
good time in your life.
Why, sir?
l told you. There is
a problem with you.
What, sir?
l will tell you some other time.
Have this. l mean let's go.
Now what do l tell you, sir?
Mr. Ranvir was a great man, sir.
He didn't differentiate
between humans and animals.
He loved humans as much
as he loved animals, sir.
l still don't believe
that Mr. Ranvir is no more.
Why are you crying?
Sir, you peeled the orange.
lts juice got into my eyes.
The next question.
How was the relationship
between Rajiv and Ranvir?
Sir! Sir! They could even lay
down their lives for each other.
They were like Bharat and Ram, sir.
lt means both were step-brothers.
Yes, sir. Both were step-brothers.
Sir, were Bharat and
Ram step-brothers too?
Yes.
Sir.. do you want to ask
me any other question?
Orange is over. End of
interrogation. Give me.
Sir, you are a genius.
You asked as many questions..
..as the orange slices.
Can l get a pomegranate?
Yes.
Sir's 2-3 questions fell down.
Officers.
Search..
..every corner of this office. Okay?
Okay. Thank you.
May l come in?
Come.
Thank you so much.
Mr. Rajiv, l have completed my
interrogation with your staff.
And l am 99 percent satisfied.
Pomegranate?
lt means you still
have 1 percent doubt.
Yes. Whenever a big property
is involved or when money..
..is involved, l don't
know why l feel suspicious.
The ranch house
you are thinking of..
..is mortgaged with the bank.
l know. But l am talking
about Ranvir's insurance policy..
..which will give you 100 million.
lnspector, my father had an
insurance policy in both our names.
l had forgotten about this.
l am eating pomegranate so
do you think l'm a fool?
You must have
thought of the policy once!
What are you trying to say?
Look, l am not accusing you.
lf you felt bad about it..
..then l am sorry.
Lowly man!
Did you say anything?
No.
You see, whenever l
interrogate somebody..
..people often call me a lowly man.
But l don't mind.
But where crime is concerned,
l am a lowly man.
Such a big incident
occurred and nobody informed me!
Why didn't anybody inform me?
Why didn't you tell me anything?
Why don't you people say something?
Listen! Come here! Who is she?
She is Sophia ma'am,
Mr. Ranvir's secretary.
Being a secretary why
is she crying so much?
How did all this happen?
Excuse me. l am RD.
The investigating
officer of this case.
l regret your boss' death.
Boss? He was not my boss.
He was my husband.
Husband?
What are you saying?
When did you marry Ranvir?
When we went to Cape Town,
we got married there.
We were going to
throw a surprise bash..
..and give this news to everybody.
Ms. Sophia, l want to ask
you a few questions alone.
Come with me. Come.
Can you tell me in detail
how this happened suddenly?
Ranvir was dependent on
me since the beginning.
He would tell me all his problems.
l too liked his company.
He was depressed for
the past 3 months..
..because of his brother.
We had to go to Cape Town to
sell Ranvir's ancestral property.
Hi!
- Hi!
There the estate agent
introduced us to the client.
He wanted to buy this property.
The deal was fixed.
The client asked for 2
days to make the payment.
That day we both were free.
We spent these 2 days together.
Ranvir was really happy.
l felt as if he had
forgotten all his problems.
That day, Ranvir proposed to me.
♫ Showing me fake dreams.. ♫
♫ ..he bluffs. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Showing me fake dreams.. ♫
♫ ..he bluffs. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Hey, mister. You say
you want me as your lover. ♫
♫ But tell me now are you a player? ♫
♫ Say what? ♫
♫ Whenever l see you, l get wounded. ♫
♫ You are in my heart and in
my every breath, beloved. ♫
♫ What spell has my
beloved cast on me? ♫
♫ Love is the game l want to play. ♫
♫ l am craving for your body now. ♫
♫ Showing me fake dreams.. ♫
♫ ..he bluffs. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Give me all the love now. ♫
♫ Showing me fake dreams.. ♫
♫ ..he bluffs. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Give me all the love now. ♫
♫ How do l express my feelings? ♫
♫ l know all the
ruses of my beloved. ♫
♫ How do l express my feelings? ♫
♫ l know all the
ruses of my beloved. ♫
♫ Stealing my solace.. ♫
♫ ..he harasses me. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Stealing my solace.. ♫
♫ ..he harasses me. My foolish,
deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Breaths are wavering.
My desires are crazy. ♫
♫ l feel like touching
your wet lips all the time. ♫
♫ What problem is this? ♫
♫ How do l say? ♫
♫ l might go crazy in this trance. ♫
♫ l am in a trance. l
am not in my senses. ♫
♫ Love is the game l want to play. ♫
♫ l am craving for your body now. ♫
♫ Showing me fake dreams he bluffs. ♫
♫ My foolish, deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Give me all the love now. ♫
♫ Showing me fake dreams he bluffs. ♫
♫ My foolish, deceiving beloved. ♫
♫ Give me all the love now. ♫
l was so happy. l felt like
the luckiest girl in the world.
Ranvir wanted to give me a surprise.
He took me to a
marriage registrar's office.
We got married there.
l didn't know that my
happiness would last just for a day.
Can l see your marriage certificate?
Can l keep this for verification?
Yes.
Thank you. Thank you
for your cooperation.
Sophia!
How dare you come here!
You killed my Ranvir!
And now you have come
here to show sympathy!
Sophia! Ranvir was my brother!
Because of you, he died! l
don't want to see your face!
Just get out of here! Get out!
Get out!
Did you observe something?
Yes, sir! Today you're
eating half a kg of strawberry!
What an observation!
- Thank you, sir!
Hello, Mr. Rajiv!
You have come here too?
lt's my habit.
Dogs and policemen are
always after someone!
l am not in the mood to
hear your stupid jokes.
Seeing his mood l remembered a song.
The bee ripened the fruit..
..and the Princess
took away the fruit.
But l don't understand. Which
fruit are you talking about?
l will explain.
This policy of 100
million dollars is a big fruit.
lf, to have this fruit,
Rajiv has killed Ronny..
..Ranvir's wife Sophia
will get this fruit.
And even if it's really an
accident and Rajiv is innocent..
..only Sophia will get this fruit.
Why are you saying
this again and again?
We are not interested in the money!
Sonia!
Yes! The grapes are sour!
Sir, you are eating
strawberry and not grapes!
Thank you. Let's go now.
- Okay.
Sonia! l have made a fool
proof plan for 100 million.
lf you help me, l will
give you 20 million.
l didn't get even 20 rupees.
Being Ranvir's widow
is more beneficial..
..than being your wife!
Without doing anything,
Sophia became a millionaire.
Now divorce me and liberate me!
Shut up!
The insurance money is
mine and l alone will get it.
lmpossible!
This won't happen as
long as Sophia is alive!
Everything is possible!
Franko!
Hello, Mr. Rajiv.
This place is not
good for welcoming you.
What has brought you here?
Ranvir is no more.
l want a girl dead.
Her photo and address are in this.
This time, there
should be no mistake.
Don't worry.
Not everybody is lucky
like Ranvir to escape from me.
l will tell you when to do it.
Sweetheart, money.
Who is she?
You don't worry about that.
She is my wife.
Don't worry. The work will be done.
You scared me!
l thought we will have some thrill..
..before receiving
100 million dollars.
How is my baby girl?
Come to daddy.
Do you know what is
common between you and me?
That we both are nude.
There is one more thing.
We both love height.
A height from where
everything looks small.
This place too is at such a height.
l love this place.
Now this bungalow is yours.
Ages ago this bungalow used to
belong to my daddy's friend.
Ranvir and l used to
come here to play.
As kids, we used to have a
cycle race on this road.
The race between Ranvir
and me began from here.
Come on Ronny, catch me.
Come on, ride is fast. Faster.
Faster, Rajiv.
Brother, slow.
No, Rajiv, try to catch me.
Ranvir always used to win.
Daddy used to give a
party to celebrate.
l used to feel really bad.
But l never cried.
l would think how to defeat Ranvir.
But Ranvir won daddy's
trust faster than me.
After daddy's death,
l found that he had..
..transferred his business,
property..
..everything in Ranvir's name.
ln my own house, l
became a second class citizen.
Whenever l wanted something..
..l had to implore Ranvir for it.
He would lovingly
give me everything.
But he also made me
realize that l am lowly..
..and he is great.
His love became my hatred for him.
ln the end hatred won.
ln the race of life l
defeated him permanently.
Forget the past.
Now everything will
be fine in our lives.
The inspector will file his report.
And we will receive
our insurance money.
There is only one problem. Sonia.
When she finds that we're together..
..she will try to create problems.
What problems will she create?
l made her give her
own death contract.
'l will tell you when to do it.'
'Sweetheart, money.'
Oh, so sad! But when
will he kill Sonia?
After receiving the
insurance's sanction letter.
Now there is only one man
between us and the money.
Officer RD.
Cut it carefully.
Fruits are very delicate.
Sir! Sir, the lab report
of the marriage certificate.
And this is 100 per
cent authentic, sir.
Ranvir and Sophia's signatures..
..are 100 per cent authentic.
Thank you. You may leave.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Mini.. assume that we
are getting married.
No, sir! l don't accept it.
ldiot, l am not proposing to you!
- So?
l am telling you to imagine!
lmagine that we are getting married.
Why should l imagine you?
Why not Brad Pitt?
Do you think you are Angelina Jolie?
l am talking about the case.
Assume that we are getting married.
ln the marriage registrar's office.
And this is the
marriage certificate.
Now you sign. Why
did you take my pen?
l'd have had to open my
purse and search for a pen.
And your pen was
right here. So l took it.
Right! This is what
people normally do.
But in this marriage certificate,
one signature..
..is done with an ink pen
and the other with a ball pen.
What do you mean?
l mean you book two
tickets for Cape Town.
Why, sir?
Because that place is
famous for coconuts.
The coconut will break. And
the truth will be revealed.
Oh!
Are you sure?
Yes. Mr. Ranvir and his
secretary Sophia had come there.
He had finalized a
deal with his client.
Were they both
here till the evening?
Not both, sir.
Only Mr. Ranvir was
here till the evening.
ln the afternoon, his
secretary suddenly fell ill.
And she returned to the hotel.
Thank you for your cooperation.
How far is the
marriage bureau from here?
lt's nearby, sir.
But today is Sunday. So it's closed.
Yes.
Now?
Now what? lt will open tomorrow.
We will go there tomorrow.
What else?
Sir, what will we do today?
Today? Today we will
take a tour of Cape Town.
Sir, what happened? Why are
you looking at me like this?
Mini, how do you find me?
A genius, sir.
l know that.
So many times l have told you
not to repeat things l know.
l feel embarrassed.
Say something else.
Sir, shall l ask you something?
Yes. Go ahead.
ln the marriage certificate you
saw the difference between inks.
But l didn't. Sir, why is my
mind not sharp like yours?
Because there is a big
problem with you, Mini.
Sir, you say this every time.
Today you have to tell
me what my problem is.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Sir, how can l have a boyfriend?
l am with you the whole day.
That's your problem!
You have crossed the
silver jubilee of life!
And you neither have a boyfriend..
..nor are you married.
Sir, even you are not married.
Yes. But l have danced a lot
in other people's marriages.
Look, Mini. Our body
needs not just food..
..but many other things.
Without that there is
frustration in the body.
You can't concentrate on your work.
l don't understand.
There are some things
which can't be explained.
You have to do it practically.
Let's go inside. l
will explain to you. Come.
Assume that your
boyfriend is with you.
He comes near you.
He holds your hand.
He pulls you towards him.
Sir, from left or right?
- Just come.
How do you feel?
lt feels nice.
Then he kisses your cheeks.
Sir, left side or right side?
Any side!
Now how does it feel?
- Sir, very nice.
Then he kisses your lips.
Sir! Here there is no left side.
So we should stop.
Why? You don't like me?
Sir, it's not that. l
consider you as my God.
Now that's a new one!
And we worship God. And not
love him. Right, sir? Bye.
ldiot!
Now how to explain to her that
this God wants to hug his devotee.
Mr. Max.
Please have a seat.
He'll be here in 5 minutes.
Okay.
Am l your father's servant?
You've begotten children!
Did you do me a favor?
Wasn't l involved in that?
l am in the office. l
have some respect here.
What do you think of me?
Having children!
Could you beget kids without me?
Talking nonsense! You
will tell my father!
You're a wife,
behave like one! Shut up!
Tell me.
Look we..
- Want to get married.
Nowadays guys are
marrying each other..
..and so are girls.
What has happened to you both?
What has affected both of you?
l say instead of getting
married and bringing a wife..
..don't feel bad,
buy a mobile phone!
Buy a mobile phone!
lf you talk from one mobile, the
other mobile doesn't get angry.
Got it? Don't mind it, sister.
You can keep it on silent mode.
But what will you do with your wife?
You can change its ring tone.
l say, sister, don't feel bad.
A wife has only one tone.
Sorry, sister. A wife
doesn't come into your grasp.
You can hold this. Even
keep it in your pocket.
You can even exchange it.
You can sell the old
piece and buy a new one.
But a wife is an old piece.
How long will you use her?
Don't mind, sister. A
wife is like a chewing gum.
Thank you.
lnitially you find it sweet.
Then you just chew it.
lf you too want to
chew all your life..
..then fill the form,
l will sign on it.
l am R.D..
R.D. Burman! Music director!
l am your big fan!
l am alive because
l hear your music.
Otherwise l would have died, Mr. RD.
l am not that RD. RD
means Robert D'Costa.
lnspector Robert D'Costa!
lnspector? My wife has sent you!
Look, it's only a small quarrel.
lt's not a fight. l
am not a criminal.
l am a nice husband.
At times, there is
a misunderstanding.
Wife and husband..
l have come here regarding a case.
Another case.
And l want to ask
you a few questions.
Okay.
Show him the snap.
Sandal on the head..
l am holding it upside down.
Do you know her?
Yes! She had come to me a
few days ago to get married.
With this guy?
No, no! He looks like a decent guy!
But the guy she married..
..was hot tempered.
He beat my photographer.
He snatched the camera
and broke it. Very bad!
What did he look like?
He had two legs, two ears,
two eyes and one nose.
He looked like a man.
l am not lying.
You have to come to Durban with us.
There, our
department's artist will..
..draw a sketch based
on your description.
l don't have a
problem in coming, sir.
But if you want a sketch
then l have his photo.
Draw the sketch from the photo.
You have his photo?
Yes! Yes!
We click shady people's
snaps with our secret camera.
We clicked his photo. Here.
Sir, he is Rajiv!
But why did he marry Sophia?
Rajiv is really smart. He
has plotted a nice plan.
This is nothing. My
wife does better things.
Look at me. l was 6 feet tall.
Now l am 5 feet tall.
Thank you.
- Welcome, sir. Pardon me, sister.
Good morning!
lf you people want,
you all can join us.
lnspector..
Please come!
What a nice surprise! Ma'am!
You see, after Ranvir's death..
..Sophia was feeling very lonely.
So you know, l thought..
..we'll stroll on
the beach hand in hand.
So cute!
- Yes! Really cute!
Such a nice brother-in-law!
He doesn't let his sister-in-law
feel his brother's absence.
But l feel you should
have waited for sometime.
l know this place is
away from the city.
But you shouldn't have
taken such a big risk.
At least till the time you
received the policy money.
Some fruits?
What are you trying to say?
Saw that, Mini?
This is the specialty of
intelligent criminals.
They never give up.
Yesterday, l went to Cape Town.
l met an estate agent there.
The one whom brother Ranvir
and sister-in-law had met.
There, suddenly
sister-in-law fell ill.
Neither she was free for two
days nor Ranvir proposed her.
Ranvir told sister-in-law
to go and rest in the hotel.
But she was in a
hurry to get married.
She reached the marriage registrar.
Mr. Rajiv was already there.
And they got married.
But Ranvir's signature is
on the marriage certificate!
How did this happen?
Because of her!
She had already taken
Ranvir's signature..
..on the marriage certificate.
'So many times l've told you
not to call me in the office.'
'Hang on! Here. Sign.'
Then our naive sister-in-law
changed the original certificate..
..to the one signed by Ranvir.
Then in the registrar's office
she gave her real signature.
And Mr. Purshottam
pretended to sign.
Now who is Purshottam?
Mr. Rajiv is Purshottam.
Didn't you book the air
ticket to Cape Town in this name?
That day 91 people
went to Cape Town.
l spoke to 90 people.
But l didn't get any
clues about Purshottam.
But l did get the photo
from the marriage bureau.
How much will you take?
What made you think that
l will accept a bribe?
Don't insult my intelligence..
officer.
lf you hadn't wanted money..
..by now l'd have
been in the lockup.
He is right! You are right!
l will take 25 per
cent of the total amount.
8 per cent service tax waived.
Till then l will eat fruits.
Done. ln return you
will give us a clean chit.
So that we get the
policy money quickly.
l have given the clean chit.
And your.. sanction
letter too is ready.
l will wait for your call. Bye.
Bye, sister-in-law.
Ma'am!
Sir, l couldn't have even imagined.
You're usually after 5-10 lakhs.
This time it's 25 per
cent of 100 million dollars!
lt means 25 million dollars.
You don't worry.
Like always you will get your money.
Along with that, 1 hundred as tip.
- Thank you, sir.
Mention not.
Sanction letter? Sophia Singh.
How did it come to Rajiv.
Did you see her?
- You bet!
Hello.
Where should l deliver your money?
There is a children's
society at King Cross road.
Go there and donate
my share of money.
Donate?
lt's my money. lt's my money.
l can do anything with it.
Good luck.
Franco?
Wake up and feel the pace.
Don't stand up as this is race.
Run, Sonia!
Now stay like this for sometime.
Today for the first time,
l see fear on your face.
You are looking very pretty.
Ronny.. l never
faced death so closely.
When l am with you,
why are you scared?
When you told me about the
sanction letter in Sophia's name..
..l understood!
That Rajiv will try to kill
you after receiving the money.
But Rajiv has already
withdrawn the money from the bank.
l know. This is what l wanted.
After all it's the
money of my death.
So how can Rajiv take it?
Everything is under control.
The plan is working.
♫ Oh yeah! l want to
get going like this. ♫
♫ Show me what you've got.
C'mon, show me what it's like. ♫
♫ Show me what you've got. ♫
♫ C'mon, show me what it's like.
Show me, l'm loving it. ♫
♫ The race of breath. ♫
♫ The race of love. ♫
♫ The race of heartbeats. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
♫ The race of breath. ♫
♫ The race of love. ♫
♫ The race of heartbeats. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
♫ Your intoxication
takes me on a high. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ l feel. ♫
♫ We endured the craving
of desires for so long. ♫
♫ We didn't tell
anybody about our plight. ♫
♫ Now l want to live in
the shade of your tresses. ♫
♫ l can even lay
down my life for you. ♫
♫ Your charms have robbed me. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Now it's not possible to separate. ♫
♫ My life is nothing without you. ♫
♫ l dream about you. l desire you. ♫
♫ l desire the
feeling of your presence. ♫
♫ My heart is crazy for you. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
Hello, sir.
- Good afternoon.
l'd like to make a
donation to the orphanage.
Sir, you've given
donation so much for these kids.
Thank you.
l've given the money to
the orphanage manager.
Thanks, buddy.
Now enjoy the rest of
your life. Okay? Bye.
Sir, it's for you.
Thank you.
You are most welcome.
Sir, why did you take the money..
..through the orphanage?
lf we had taken it directly,
we wouldn't have had..
..to give money to the manager.
lf you accept bribe in
the name of a good cause..
..then there is no fear of
being slandered or being caught.
l was afraid.
l thought you've really reformed..
..and are being so charitable.
Charity begins at home, Sayang.
As you sow so shall you reap!
So do your deed
according to the fruits..
..you want to reap.
Now l won't eat fruits. l
will eat only dry fruits.
Oh Rajiv, today we will celebrate.
Celebration on our victory.
Okay? - You are the boss,
baby. - Thank you.
Ages ago this bungalow used to
belong to my daddy's friend.
Ranvir and l used to
come here to play.
As kids we used to have
cycle race on this road.
The race between Ranvir
and me began from here.
Ranvir always used to win.
Daddy used to give a
party to celebrate.
l used to feel really bad.
But l never cried.
l would think how to defeat Ranvir.
But Ranvir won daddy's
trust faster than me.
After daddy's death l found that..
..he had transferred the business,
property, in Ranvir's name.
And in my own house l
became a second class citizen.
Whenever l wanted something..
..l had to implore to Ranvir.
He would lovingly
give me everything.
But he also made me
realize that l am lowly..
..and he is great.
His love became my hatred for him.
ln the end hatred won.
ln the race of life l
defeated him permanently.
What's the matter, Rajiv?
The race is still not over..
..and you've declared the result.
You're thinking that l had
fallen from the terrace.
There's a difference
between falling and dying.
You saw only what l showed you.
Not yours but my plan was working.
You were watching my every movement.
And l was keeping a
tab on your every move.
l'd have never found out..
..if you had not received
that call in the hospital.
'Hello.
- Hello Mr. Rajiv.
l am Franco speaking.
'Why did you call me?'
For the money.
'Money? For what?'
'Ronnie is alive. He didn't die.
Nothing has happened to him.'
'l told you he shouldn't
survive at any cost. No.'
'You won't do anything. Now l
will do what is to be done.'
After returning home
from the hospital..
..l searched your bedroom.
There l found Sonia's file.
l wondered how did
you got Sonia's file..
..when you have not even met her.
l understood.
That you'll use
Sonia to kill me again.
But before you could befriend
Sonia, l gave her hand in yours.
That was not sacrificing my love.
l wanted to know your plan.
Sorry, Rajiv.
The man you gave the
contract to kill me..
..has himself died.
Consider it as a gift from me.
You are still alive
because before killing you..
..l want to know why
you wanted to kill me.
When l found that your
plan is of 100 million..
..l made a plan of 200 million.
For the people, l died first.
So that you could get 100 million.
And then after killing you, l will
get yours and my death's 200 million.
But you turned out to be smarter.
You didn't let me get a clue..
..that you and Sophia are together.
And after my death you even
proved that Sophia is my wife.
So that the police
don't suspect you.
And the insurance money is
transferred in Sophia's name.
And you.. Mrs. Ranvir Singh.
Touch me, touch me.
Kiss me, kiss me.
You are a fine actress.
You should have been in Hollywood.
l had to wait till the money was
transferred in Sophia's account.
And during this
period l found out that..
..you didn't do all
this just for the money.
There was rancor in your
heart and mind for me.
Since childhood you
wanted to defeat me.
You should have told
me once, lovingly.
l would've deliberately lost.
Enough!
This is what l hate! This love!
This fake love
reminds me every time..
..that l am your step-brother!
l was deliberately losing.
l wanted to defeat
you on my own merit!
You could never win
because you were..
..always thinking of defeating me.
And l never lost because l
always thought of winning.
Today too, in the
attempt to defeat me..
..you yourself have lost.
Yes, l lost. But what did you think?
That you will lecture me
and l'll fall at your feet..
..and beg for my life?
You want to kill me?
Come on! Kill me!
Kill me!
Come on!
l want to remove your rancor.
All your life you wanted to
defeat me on your own merit.
So fine! Today let's have
another race. A last race.
As kids we would have a cycle race.
Today let's have the race of life.
And the one who wins..
will get everything.
What are you saying, Ranvir?
You are giving him another chance?
Sonia, please.
lt's between us.
What do you say, Rajiv? 200 million.
Or.. or nothing.
♫ The race of breath. ♫
♫ The race of love. ♫
♫ The race of heartbeats. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
Let's do it.
Wow, what a sports car.
Are you ready?
Anybody can win in this car.
Not the car but the
driver wins the race.
No breaks!
What?
Elder brother! Are the
brakes functioning fine?
See you in hell.
l too will come there.
But after 50-60 years.
lt is Ronny.
Ronny, my friend! Any last wish?
You are wrong, Rajiv.
We won't meet after 50-60 years.
But we will meet after 5-6 minutes.
ls that so? How?
There is a bomb in your car.
Remember jockey Monto?
Now don't apply the brake.
lf the car's speed is less than
100 then your car will explode.
Now neither l nor you can stop.
My brake is not working. And
you can't apply the brakes.
♫ Race. ♫
Ranvir!
Hang on!
♫ Race. ♫
l raced with honesty.
But today Rajiv betrayed me again.
l didn't plant any bomb in the car.
Wow! Not just the younger brother..
..but even the elder
brother is very smart.
Sir, this story has ended.
No, Mini. This story
is still not over.
The end is still left.
Come, big brother.
Mini, there are 200
million dollars in his car.
His 100 million and 100
million of his poor late brother.
Why don't l kill him
and seize all the money?
As it is he is dead
for the world. Right?
Drop the gun. l am only
afraid of honest people.
'l won't die. He will die.'
'Yes, Ranvir here.'
'Yes, dude. Tell me.'
'l want to meet you.'
'Fine, we will meet in
the evening in the club.'
'And you will have to
arrange for a dead body..
..which you could
easily prove as my corpse.'
'Don't worry, partner.'
'Money can make
everything possible.'
'l still love you, Ronny. But 20
million dollar is a big amount.'
l am sorry.
'l guess this is where
we say goodbye, Ronny.'
We've pulled the biggest
scam of the century, dude.
Sonia.. give him his share.
Take your money. Keep it in the car.
lt was fun working with you. Bye.
Bye.
Sir, l have never
seen such a big amount.
lt's our hard earned money.
Open the bag and check.
Sir, bomb!
lf you had tried to kill me,
you too wouldn't have survived.
l hope we never meet again.
Smart boy.
♫ lt's hot! ♫
♫ lt's hot! l want to
get it right here. ♫
♫ lt's hot! ♫
♫ Show me it's hot. ♫
♫ C'mon, stand up like a man.' ♫
♫ Yeah, it's so hot. Soul. ♫
♫ So hot! ♫
♫ Race on my mind. ♫
♫ Race is in my soul. ♫
♫ Race is in my life. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
♫ Race on my mind. ♫
♫ Race is in my soul. ♫
♫ Race is in my life. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
♫ Your intoxication
takes me on a high. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ So hot! ♫
♫ Oh, when you're touching my body.
Oh, you're simply driving me crazy. ♫
♫ You know what,
there's no need to worry.. ♫
♫ ..l'll smack it up and take it down,
till we get dirty. ♫
♫ You know what, l kind of like it,
in the bedroom or anywhere like it. ♫
♫ l feel that when you're kissing my
neck, l feel l just can't take it. ♫
♫ This smoldering of desires. ♫
♫ l am burning like the sun. ♫
♫ No matter what my plight was. ♫
♫ l fought but never won. ♫
♫ ln the shade of your tresses. ♫
♫ That's where l want to stay. ♫
♫ lf you ask. ♫
♫ l will give my heart away. ♫
♫ l am high, so high, l could fly. ♫
♫ That's just how you make me feel. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ Move your body like enigma. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ We don't want to live this way. ♫
♫ My life. ♫
♫ l live for you everyday. ♫
♫ l dream about you. l desire you. ♫
♫ l am never feeling down,
as long as you're around. ♫
♫ My heart is crazy for you. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ Race on my mind. ♫
♫ Race is in my soul. ♫
♫ Race is in my life. ♫
♫ My heart is racing on. ♫
♫ Your intoxication
takes me on a high. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ O Allah! ♫
♫ There is restlessness everywhere. ♫
♫ Separation is difficult. ♫
♫ ln your love. ♫
♫ lts hot! ♫